<div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" id="about">
    <h1>About the Electronic Edition</h1>
    <p>The Office of the Historian at the U.S. Department of State has embarked on a program to
        release an ebook edition of the <em>Foreign Relations of the United States</em>
            (<em>FRUS</em>) series, which was established in 1861. Far lighter and more portable
        than printed editions of <em>FRUS</em>, the ebook edition offers the full content of each
        volume and makes use of the full-text search and other reading features of most ebook
        devices and applications, including bookmarking and note-taking. Unlike the web-based
        edition of <em>FRUS</em>, the ebook edition, once downloaded, can be accessed even without
        internet connectivity.</p>
    <p>In creating the <em>FRUS</em> ebook edition, we endeavored to maintain fidelity with the
        original printed edition. One challenge in this respect is representing original page
        numbers from printed editions in ebooks. For readers who need to cite material in this
        ebook, we recommend citing document numbers instead of page numbers, since document numbers
        are persistent, media-neutral identifiers. In older <em>FRUS</em> volumes (before the
        subseries covering the Johnson administration), where cross references use page numbers
        rather than document numbers, we append to each page number a bracketed list of the document
        numbers that correspond to it.</p>
    <p>The Office of the Historian has worked to ensure that this ebook is error-free and works on a
        broad range of devices. Please email <a
            href="mailto:history_ebooks@state.gov?subject=FRUS%20ebooks%20Feedback&amp;body=Your%20e-reader%3A%0A%0AVolume%3A%0A%0AComments%3A"
            >history_ebooks@state.gov</a> with any feedback.</p>
    <p>To learn about updates to this ebook, other ebooks, and the ebook initiative in general,
        visit our <a href="http://history.state.gov/historicaldocuments/ebooks">ebooks homepage</a>,
        and follow us on Twitter at <a href="http://twitter.com/HistoryAtState">@HistoryAtState</a>
        and Tumblr at <a href="http://HistoryAtState.tumblr.com">HistoryAtState</a>.</p>
    <p style="text-align: right; font-weight: bold;">Office of the Historian<br/> Bureau of Public
        Affairs<br/> U.S. Department of State<br/>
        <span class="ho:generate-month-year"/></p>
</div>
